Philip Henry Sheridan Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1863-1891 (Box 90-95, Reel 87-94)
  - Forsyth, George A., Europe-Asia observation tour (Box 90, Reel 87)
    - 1876
    - 1875
    - 1876
    - 1876
    - 1876
    - 1875-1876
  - Indian affairs (Box 91, Reel 88)
    - 1869-1876
    - 1876 (Box 91, Reel 89)
    - 1876-1877 (Box 91, Reel 90)
    - 1876-1877 (Box 91, Reel 91)
    - 1868-1875 (Box 92, Reel 91)
    - 1877
    - 1878
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
    - 1885-1886
    - 1891
    - Undated
  - Page, Henry, telegram books, quartermaster, Army of the Potomac (Box 93, Reel 91)
    - 1863, July-1864, Oct.
    - 1864, Oct.-Dec. (Box 93, Reel 92)
    - 1864, Dec. 16-1865, Jan. 10
    - 1865, Jan. 11-Mar. 10
    - 1865, Mar. 11-Apr. 12 (Box 93, Reel 93)
    - 1865, Apr. 13-June 22
  - Piegan expedition, 1869-1870 (Box 94, Reel 93)
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - Warren, Gouverneur K., court of inquiry, 1880-1883
    - 1 of 6
    - 2 of 6
    - 3 of 6
    - 4 of 6 (Box 94, Reel 94)
    - 5 of 6
    - 6 of 6
  - Wright, Rebecca, federal spy, Winchester, Va., 1864 (Box 95, Reel 94)
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Reconnaissance of the Bighorn Mountains and the valleys of the Bighorn and Yellowstone rivers, 1877
    - 1 of 7
    - 2 of 7
    - 3 of 7
    - 4 of 7
    - 5 of 7
    - 6 of 7
    - 7 of 7
- Book and Speech File, 1878-circa 1883 (Box 96-109, Reel 94-100)
  Drafts of memoirs and speeches.
  The memoirs are arranged by volume and chapter and the speeches chronologically.
  - Memoirs, undated (Box 96, Reel 94)
    - Vol. 1
      - Chapter 1
      - Chapter 2
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 3
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 4
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 5 (Box 97, Reel 95)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 6
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 7
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 8 (Box 98, Reel 95)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 9
      - Chapter 10
      - Chapter 11
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 12 (Box 99, Reel 95)
      - Chapter 13
        - 2 of 2
        - 1 of 2 (Box 99, Reel 96)
      - Chapter 14
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 15 (Box 100, Reel 96)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 16
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 17
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 18 (Box 101, Reel 96)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 19
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 20
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 21
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 22 (Box 102, Reel 97)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 23
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 24
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
    - Vol. 2 (Box 103, Reel 97)
      - Chapter 1
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 2
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 3
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 4 (Box 104, Reel 98)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 5
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 6
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 7
      - Chapter 8 (Box 105, Reel 98)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 9
        - 1 of 6
        - 2 of 6
        - 3 of 6
        - 4 of 6
        - 5 of 6
        - 6 of 6
      - Chapter 10 (Box 106, Reel 99)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 11
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 12
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 13 (Box 107, Reel 99)
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 14
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 15
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Chapter 16 (Box 108, Reel 100)
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 17
      - Chapter 18
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 19 (Box 109, Reel 100)
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Chapter 20
        - 1 of 3
        - 2 of 3
        - 3 of 3
      - Fragments
  - Speeches, 1878-circa 1883
- Miscellany, 1853-1896 (Box 110-113, Reel 101-103)
  Biographical material, citations, charges and specifications against Sheridan, commissions, contingent fund records, memorabilia, newspaper clippings, personal financial records, printed matter, and expressions of sympathy.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Biographical material, 1882-1888, undated (Box 110, Reel 101)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Citations, 1865-1871
  - Charges and specifications, 1862
  - Commissions, 1853-1869 See Oversize
  - Contingent fund records
    - 1872-1873
    - 1874-1884, undated
  - General, 1873, undated (Box 111, Reel 101)
  - Maps, 1871-1884
  - Newspaper clippings, 1875-1878, undated
  - Personal financial records (Box 112, Reel 101)
    - 1869-1875
    - 1875-1878 (Box 112, Reel 102)
    - 1878-1882
    - 1869-1888 (Box 113, Reel 103)
  - Printed matter, 1855-1896, undated
  - Sympathy expressions, 1888 (Box 113, Reel 103)
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
- Scrapbooks, 1861-1881 (Box 114-116, Reel 104)
  Mounted newspaper clippings.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1861, May-1862, Aug., Cincinnati Daily Commercial (Box 114, Reel 104)
  - 1863, Jan.-June, Cincinnati Daily Commercial (Box 115, Reel 104)
  - 1874, Apr.-1881, Feb., various newspapers (Box 116, Reel 104)
- Oversize, 1853-1869 (Box OV 1, Reel 104)
  Commissions.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Miscellany (Box OV 1, Reel 104)
    - Commissions, 1853-1869 (Container 110)